<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jagar</title>
    <link>https://jagar.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jagar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 08:57:46 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jagar.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android retrofit with Python API example</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/android_retrofit_with_python_api_example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 08:57:46 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/android_retrofit_with_python_api_example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial we will demonstrate how to connect an android app with a Python 3.x based RESTful API using retrofit 2 and PHP Slim framework.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a skeleton loading view for any recyclerView or view in Android</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/how_to_create_skeleton_loading_view_for_any_recyclervie_or_view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:04:44 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/how_to_create_skeleton_loading_view_for_any_recyclervie_or_view/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In these few steps we will find out how to implement the Skeleton View for the views and the recycler views in Android which is used these days in some of the most famous apps like the loading views in Facebook app.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a gradle project with javaFX in intellij</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/how_to_create_a_gradle_project_with_javafx_in_intellij/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 21:21:38 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/how_to_create_a_gradle_project_with_javafx_in_intellij/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We will in few steps how we can work on javaFX within a gradle project in the new intellij build 2019.2 which may apply other builds too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to open an app using a dialer call in Android Studio</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/open-an-app-using-dialer-in-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 08:51:25 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/open-an-app-using-dialer-in-android/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We will explain in few easy steps how to keep your app&amp;rsquo;s icon hidden in the main menu, and how to open it only by dialing a specific code  in the default android dialer. You can also let the user specify his own dialer number to open your app.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create Mind Mapping View (Hierarchy view) in Android Studio Easily</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/mindmappingviewandroid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 10:39:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/mindmappingviewandroid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial we will explain an easy way to create and customize a mind mapping, hierarchy or tree view in android studio using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/JagarYousef/Mindo&#34;&gt;Mindo&lt;/a&gt; android library, which brings an easy approach to implement this with its full functionality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use camera and capture photos in your app without using any other apps in Android Studio (using camera2)</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/opencamera2window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 08:41:44 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/opencamera2window/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial we will go step-by-step on how to implement camera2 in our android app through opening a dialog with camera view, capturing a picture and display it in an ImageView without the need to open the default camera app or any other app in Android studio. This will add a great functionality to your apps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The easiest and best way to pass data (arguments) between controllers in JavaFX</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/passingdatainjavafx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 09:44:58 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/passingdatainjavafx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of programs in this world would need to pass different data and arguments between the different layouts and screens, so we will explain the easiest way to have this done in JavaFX in this tutorial.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a view for voice messages in Android</title>
      <link>https://jagar.me/post/voicemessagesview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 14:17:58 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jagar.me/post/voicemessagesview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we will go step-by-step in implementing an easy voice player in Android and avoid all those android&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;MediaPlayer&lt;/em&gt; unwanted errors. So this could be a good option to be out there in your chat app.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>